<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><UpdatedPropertyDetails:updatedPropertyDetails xmlns:UpdatedPropertyDetails="http://www.zillow.com/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.zillow.com/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd http://www.zillowstatic.com/vstatic/ca33129/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><request><zpid>115828709</zpid></request><message><text>Request successfully processed</text><code>0</code></message><response><zpid>115828709</zpid><pageViewCount><currentMonth>487</currentMonth><total>20082</total></pageViewCount><address><street>420 Mission Bay Blvd N UNIT 1103</street><zipcode>94158</zipcode><city>San Francisco</city><state>CA</state><latitude>37.77119</latitude><longitude>-122.388247</longitude></address><posting><status>Active</status><type>Other</type><lastUpdatedDate>2015-03-22 10:09:00.0</lastUpdatedDate><externalUrl>http://www.guecogroup.com</externalUrl></posting><price currency="USD">1749000</price><links><homeDetails>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/420-Mission-Bay-Blvd-N-UNIT-1103-San-Francisco-CA-94158/115828709_zpid/</homeDetails><photoGallery>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/420-Mission-Bay-Blvd-N-UNIT-1103-San-Francisco-CA-94158/115828709_zpid/#image=lightbox%3Dtrue</photoGallery><homeInfo>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/420-Mission-Bay-Blvd-N-UNIT-1103-San-Francisco-CA-94158/115828709_zpid/</homeInfo></links><images><count>37</count><image><url>http://photos1.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISpll4v2blwl351000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IS99hgup25gr351000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISxrngd9ft4j351000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos1.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISp986myfo2j151000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISl2oekaldl2651000000000.jpg</url></image></images><editedFacts><useCode>Condominium</useCode><bedrooms>2</bedrooms><bathrooms>2.0</bathrooms><finishedSqFt>1562</finishedSqFt><yearBuilt>2012</yearBuilt><numRooms>4</numRooms></editedFacts><homeDescription>Exemplary Living in Gorgeous Mission Bay Experience the lifestyle, luxury, and convenience of unparalleled building amenities in one of Californias best-selling residential communities: Madrone by Bosa. Residence #1103 at the Madrone features luxury living at its finest. Upon entering this pristine 2 bedroom, 2 bathroom property through its formal entryway, you are greeted with a huge living area with panoramic views of the bay and adjoining park from brilliant floor-to-ceiling windows with Hunter Douglas window treatments. Beautiful hardwood floors are featured throughout the spacious main living area along with a balcony that allows for outdoor relaxation and contemplation with views of downtown. The amply appointed chefs kitchen, open to the main living area, features top-of-the-line finishes and appliances. A Bosch gas stove, Bosch dishwasher, Thermador refrigerator, Caesarstone countertops, and sleek European-inspired cabinetry allow you to dine and entertain in splendid fashion. The split layout of the residence allows for optimal privacy between bedrooms. The master bedroom features a spacious en-suite bathroom with twin sinks along with expansive closets and floor-to-ceiling windows. The second bedroom is just as spacious as the master suite and features a pop-out bay window, a perfect location for an office or study. Along with a full-sized washer and dryer and air conditioning, Residence #1103 offers unmatched finishes and fixtures that define contemporary luxury living. Come and experience all that Madrone has to offer with Residence #1103. Indulge in Madrones resort-like amenities including an open-air sun deck, 75-foot heated lap pool, fun-sized jacuzzi spa, resort-style steam room and sauna, outdoor grill and terrace lounge, social dining room with a catering kitchen, game room with flat screen TVs and billiards, private movie theater, state-of-the-art fitness studio, landscaped gardens and courtyard, attended lobby, and hotel-style reception area. Madrone is located in the heart of Mission Bay, San Franciscos newest, fastest-growing master-planned community that is welcoming new residents, retail, businesses, and parks every day. Living at Madrone you are at the center of a vibrant, walkable neighborhood surrounded by parks and open spaces, close to AT&amp;T Park, Caltrain, and Muni. 50,000 square feet of retail are currently planned for the surrounding area, including a new UCSF research hospital opening in 2015 and plans for a new sports and entertainment arena. With companies like Old Navy, Nektar, Fibrogen, and UCSF as major employers in Mission Bay, there will always be a strong demand for homes at Madrone. Unit Features: Open living/dining room with floor-to-ceiling windows Gourmet kitchen with stainless steel Bosch appliances, Caesarstone countertops, sleek European-inspired cabinetry Spacious balcony perfect for outdoor enjoyment Master bedroom with en-suite bathroom Second bedroom and bathroom Individually controlled heat and air conditioning Hardwood floors in living areas, carpet in bedrooms Whirlpool front-loading washer and dryer in unit One space in parking garage included Storage included Building Features: Open-air sun deck with 75-foot heated lap pool and jacuzzi spa Outdoor grill and terrace lounge State-of-the-art fitness studio Resort-style steam room and sauna Social dining room with catering kitchen Game room with flat screen TVs and billiards Private movie theater Business center Attended lobby and luxurious seating area Landscaped gardens and courtyard Gated parking Located close to public transportation with easy access to freeways 280/101, Caltrain and corporate shuttles Walk to the AT&amp;T stadium, UCSF campus, a farmers market, Safeway, Whole Foods, eateries, and nightlife</homeDescription></response></UpdatedPropertyDetails:updatedPropertyDetails><!-- H:002  T:64ms  S:829  R:Sat Apr 04 00:23:47 PDT 2015  B:4.0.14071-release_20150326172601-monkey.169e44a-CANDIDATE-b02fcfe-20150331.215139.169e44a3df6a78fa3c7aaf603f10471630160215.20150331175758297-origin/release/20150326172601-monkey -->