<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><UpdatedPropertyDetails:updatedPropertyDetails xmlns:UpdatedPropertyDetails="http://www.zillow.com/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.zillow.com/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd http://www.zillowstatic.com/vstatic/ca33129/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><request><zpid>20776453</zpid></request><message><text>Request successfully processed</text><code>0</code></message><response><zpid>20776453</zpid><pageViewCount><currentMonth>289</currentMonth><total>1486</total></pageViewCount><address><street>6137 W 6th St</street><zipcode>90048</zipcode><city>Los Angeles</city><state>CA</state><latitude>34.065291</latitude><longitude>-118.362758</longitude></address><posting><status>Active</status><type>Other</type><lastUpdatedDate>2015-03-25 11:33:00.0</lastUpdatedDate><externalUrl>http://www.alphonsobjorn.com</externalUrl></posting><price currency="USD">2495000</price><links><homeDetails>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/6137-W-6th-St-Los-Angeles-CA-90048/20776453_zpid/</homeDetails><photoGallery>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/6137-W-6th-St-Los-Angeles-CA-90048/20776453_zpid/#image=lightbox%3Dtrue</photoGallery><homeInfo>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/6137-W-6th-St-Los-Angeles-CA-90048/20776453_zpid/</homeInfo></links><images><count>48</count><image><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISxrjlqz6qd8wk1000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos1.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IS13b9p9qtgjwk1000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos2.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IShffxpmy9xdwk1000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IS9h3n46zw2i0h1000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos2.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IShn5zmc35bf0h1000000000.jpg</url></image></images><editedFacts><useCode>MultiFamily2To4</useCode><bedrooms>6</bedrooms><bathrooms>4.0</bathrooms><finishedSqFt>4038</finishedSqFt><lotSizeSqFt>6175</lotSizeSqFt><yearBuilt>1936</yearBuilt><yearUpdated>2007</yearUpdated><exteriorMaterial>Stucco</exteriorMaterial><parkingType>Garage - Detached</parkingType><architecture>Spanish</architecture><floorNumber>2</floorNumber><numUnits>2</numUnits></editedFacts><homeDescription>Welcome to this extensively remodeled Spanish duplex which stands on a picturesque tree lined street in the Miracle Mile. Loaded with tones of character and charm from the glamorous Hollywood era, this turnkey property has been lovingly updated and exudes pride of ownership at every turn. Just blocks away from many great restaurants, shopping streets and the famed The Grove shopping center and Farmers Market.  A block from the future home of the Oscars and the Academy Museum currently under construction, LA County Art Museum, famous La Brea Tar Pits, and the new Peterson Auto Museum.


Comprised of three bedrooms and two baths in each unit, and features many original details throughout. From the oversized living room with period stained glass windows to the graceful dining room and the central family room perfect for hosting dinner parties, each unit boast over 2,000 sq. ft. of living space. The current owners have diligently updated all systems to include, electrical, plumbing and HVAC and have tastefully restored the building without compromising the integrity of the architectural style. Both kitchens have been completely upgraded and expanded with modern day amenities. Both units have been occupied as owner users and will be delivered vacant upon the close of escrow. This duplex also features two oversized garages, and a great private outdoor entertaining area for year round dining alfresco in the great southern California climate.


An investment like this rarely comes on the market in this location. This Duplex makes for a great condo alternative/owner user or simply a great rental in a highly coveted area.



Extensive 3-year remodel

New roof with heat reflective coating
2 completely new AC/Heat systems with HEPA filters
2 new 200 amp electrical panels and rewired to code
Total rewiring and new outlets added
Lights added to closets
Both kitchens remodeled from the studs up
Copper plumbing throughout except for 1 bathroom upstairs
2nd bath in each unit has been remodeled from studs up
All windows/doors refitted and hardware was cleaned  
Second floor unit has new wood floor
Painted inside throughout and hand scraped and painted with elastomers paint outside
All wrought iron was custom made
Dimmers on all switches
Professional landscapes with mature palms planted and large privacy hedge 
Three 75-gallon water heaters
</homeDescription></response></UpdatedPropertyDetails:updatedPropertyDetails><!-- H:004  T:114ms  S:1003  R:Sun Apr 05 18:20:06 PDT 2015  B:4.0.14071-release_20150326172601-monkey.169e44a-CANDIDATE-b02fcfe-20150331.215139.169e44a3df6a78fa3c7aaf603f10471630160215.20150331175758297-origin/release/20150326172601-monkey -->