<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><UpdatedPropertyDetails:updatedPropertyDetails xmlns:UpdatedPropertyDetails="http://www.zillow.com/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.zillow.com/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd http://www.zillowstatic.com/vstatic/ca33129/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><request><zpid>2102831648</zpid></request><message><text>Request successfully processed</text><code>0</code></message><response><zpid>2102831648</zpid><pageViewCount><currentMonth>488</currentMonth><total>545</total></pageViewCount><address><street>26 Grampian Way</street><zipcode>02125</zipcode><city>Boston</city><state>MA</state><latitude>42.311595</latitude><longitude>-71.051226</longitude></address><posting><status>Active</status><type>Other</type><lastUpdatedDate>2015-04-04 08:58:00.0</lastUpdatedDate><externalUrl>http://www.savinheights.com</externalUrl></posting><price currency="USD">749000</price><links><homeDetails>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/26-Grampian-Way-Boston-MA-02125/2102831648_zpid/</homeDetails><photoGallery>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/26-Grampian-Way-Boston-MA-02125/2102831648_zpid/#image=lightbox%3Dtrue</photoGallery><homeInfo>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/26-Grampian-Way-Boston-MA-02125/2102831648_zpid/</homeInfo></links><images><count>29</count><image><url>http://photos1.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IS13b52h5zekx50000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos2.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IS5ihff2kc37f60000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IS9ppdyuy2j2c70000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISl6r3x0tvtro70000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISxzx1nlb4z2r70000000000.jpg</url></image></images><editedFacts><useCode>SingleFamily</useCode><bedrooms>4</bedrooms><bathrooms>2.5</bathrooms><finishedSqFt>2000</finishedSqFt><yearBuilt>2015</yearBuilt><view>City</view><parkingType>Garage - Attached</parkingType><heatingSources>Gas</heatingSources><heatingSystem>Forced air</heatingSystem><coolingSystem>Central</coolingSystem></editedFacts><homeDescription>(Pre-Sale Offers Accepted Soon. Contact ASAP) The Welsh Group is proud to present Boston's most unique new construction development - Savin Heights. 8 luxury townhouses that feel like single-family homes perched atop Boston's historic Savin Hill neighborhood with spectacular views of the Boston skyline. Located in a beautiful neighborhood with architecturally detailed homes, open space, recreation and easy access to the city via MBTA or highway, these residences offer the perfect mix of suburban living and city convenience. With a beach, jogging trails, an 8 acre park, a baseball field, a waterfront playground, tennis courts, two yacht clubs, a dog park, and more located within walking distance, all the recreation you need is right outside your door. Each residence will have three living levels, first floor open concept kitchen/living areas, custom kitchen cabinets, Jenn Air Pro Series stainless steel appliances, Cararra granite countertops, gas fireplaces, laundry and three beds on the second floor, third floor master suites with multiple walk-in closets and en suite bathrooms, energy efficient central heating and cooling systems, wired for surround sound, and ADT security systems with remote access for garage doors via smart phones. Four residences have attached garages with direct access to first floor. Five units have full basements. All units have 2 total off-street parking spaces. For floorplans and more information, visit www.SavinHeights.com or contact the listing agent. Pricing and availability may vary. Plans subject to change. Expected completion May 2015. ***Do not enter the site without listing agent. Active construction site***</homeDescription><whatOwnerLoves>New construction, beautiful neighborhood, spectacular views, walk to beach, master suites, ADT security systems, easy access to Boston via MBTA </whatOwnerLoves></response></UpdatedPropertyDetails:updatedPropertyDetails><!-- H:002  T:546ms  S:976  R:Mon Apr 06 11:19:35 PDT 2015  B:4.0.14071-release_20150326172601-monkey.169e44a-CANDIDATE-b02fcfe-20150331.215139.169e44a3df6a78fa3c7aaf603f10471630160215.20150331175758297-origin/release/20150326172601-monkey -->