<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><UpdatedPropertyDetails:updatedPropertyDetails xmlns:UpdatedPropertyDetails="http://www.zillow.com/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.zillow.com/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd http://www.zillowstatic.com/vstatic/ca33129/static/xsd/UpdatedPropertyDetails.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><request><zpid>83154174</zpid></request><message><text>Request successfully processed</text><code>0</code></message><response><zpid>83154174</zpid><pageViewCount><currentMonth>912</currentMonth><total>3889</total></pageViewCount><address><street>1160 Mission St UNIT 2302</street><zipcode>94103</zipcode><city>San Francisco</city><state>CA</state><latitude>37.778705</latitude><longitude>-122.412635</longitude></address><posting><status>Active</status><type>Other</type><lastUpdatedDate>2015-03-22 17:56:00.0</lastUpdatedDate><externalUrl>http://www.guecogroup.com</externalUrl></posting><price currency="USD">925000</price><links><homeDetails>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/1160-Mission-St-UNIT-2302-San-Francisco-CA-94103/83154174_zpid/</homeDetails><photoGallery>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/1160-Mission-St-UNIT-2302-San-Francisco-CA-94103/83154174_zpid/#image=lightbox%3Dtrue</photoGallery><homeInfo>http://www.zillow.com/homedetails/1160-Mission-St-UNIT-2302-San-Francisco-CA-94103/83154174_zpid/</homeInfo></links><images><count>29</count><image><url>http://photos2.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IStgs5at0ssxvf0000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos2.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISdk4d9ngfc0ns0000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos2.zillowstatic.com/p_d/IS56g6a3raqxei0000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos3.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISxzdurwm2i0fi0000000000.jpg</url><url>http://photos1.zillowstatic.com/p_d/ISptbi9qiu93fi0000000000.jpg</url></image></images><editedFacts><useCode>Condominium</useCode><bedrooms>1</bedrooms><bathrooms>1.0</bathrooms><finishedSqFt>764</finishedSqFt><yearBuilt>2007</yearBuilt><numRooms>3</numRooms></editedFacts><homeDescription>Coming Soon: Modern Luxury Penthouse with Panoramic City and Water Views This desirable 1 bedroom plus den penthouse floor plan features floor-to-ceiling glass windows, an east-facing balcony, and expanded 10-foot ceiling heights. The open concept living room/dining room/kitchen is ideal for entertaining, and the chefs kitchen offers Studio Becker cabinetry in a light espresso finish, under-cabinet and pendant designer lighting, Bosch stainless steel appliances, a vented gas range, and expansive Caesarstone countertops. The spa-like bathroom is elegantly appointed with limestone surrounds and counters, Maxstone Italian ceramic tile flooring, a rain-style shower with an upgraded glass enclosure, and Cifial fixtures. The den is perfect for an office area, recreation alcove, media room, or for a guest area. This residence has been extensively upgraded with wide-plank hardwood floors, an in-unit full capacity energy-efficient Bosch washer and dryer, Hunter Douglas window treatments, and fiber-optic wiring. SOMA Grands fifth-floor garden level features a full fitness center, hot tub, sun deck with cabanas, yoga studio, meditation garden, fire pit, barbecue area with picnic bench seating, and club room with a chefs kitchen and plasma TV. SOMA Grands luxury lifestyle services include bi-monthly housekeeping, concierge services, 24-hour security, a DVD library, Philz coffee and tea service, wireless internet in the lobby, and a wellness room for private instruction or massage. The building community also offers wine tastings, yoga and cooking classes, a book club, movie nights and special event gatherings. Residence #2302 Features:  1 bedroom plus den, 1 bathroom penthouse Large floor-to-ceiling windows Generous ceiling heights Chefs kitchen with Bosch stainless appliances, Caesarstone counters, Studio Becker German-engineered cabinetry Spa-like bathroom features limestone surrounds and counters, Maxstone ceramic tile flooring, rain-style shower with upgraded glass enclosure, Cifial fixtures Hardwood floors throughout living areas and bedrooms Fiber-optic wiring Washer and dryer in unit 1-car parking SOMA Grand Luxury Lifestyle Services The SOMA Grand staff is expertly trained in a service culture that elevates homeowners to the level of pampered hotel guests. SOMA Grand, a San Francisco luxury condo residence, is a full-service high-rise community with concierge service. The staff is hotel-trained and ready to take care of every business or personal request on demand. From dinner reservations to car service, from dog-walkers to personal shoppers, from a masseuse to a caterer, this San Francisco luxury condo property gives you access to only the best.  Twice-a-month housekeeping Concierge 24-hour security Philz coffee and tea available in lobby DVD lending library Monthly wine tastings Wireless internet in lobby and park level along with a community extranet Concierge-assisted reservations A la carte services offered at an additional charge include: SOMA Dog Certified dog trainer, spa facility, yoga and Pilates, laundry services, interior design, cooking classes, technology services, fresh flower and plant care services, child care, personal trainer/nutritionist, UPS and FedEx, doctors-on-call SOMA Grand Building Amenities Define Affordable Luxury Living beautifully no longer requires living beyond your means. Whether you are making your first real estate purchase, moving to the San Francisco Bay Area, or simply investing wisely in property for the future, SOMA Grand has been designed to allow you to live, work and play in grand style. A luxury condominium in San Francisco, the 22-story glass tower offers visual excitement, rich textures, and a polished sense of design. An eclectic mix of people combined with inspirational common areas are the bedrock for a thriving community in San Francisco. </homeDescription><neighborhood>SOMA</neighborhood><schoolDistrict>SOMA</schoolDistrict></response></UpdatedPropertyDetails:updatedPropertyDetails><!-- H:004  T:54ms  S:891  R:Sat Apr 04 00:23:46 PDT 2015  B:4.0.14071-release_20150326172601-monkey.169e44a-CANDIDATE-b02fcfe-20150331.215139.169e44a3df6a78fa3c7aaf603f10471630160215.20150331175758297-origin/release/20150326172601-monkey -->